Contact

judyrodriguez52@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/judy-rodriguez-a3b46118 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Hospitals ACLS

Certifications

Registered Nurse/Alaska
Registered Nurse/California
Registered Nurse/Massachusetts
Registered Nurse/Washington
Registered Nurse/Oregon

Judy Rodriguez

Ready for new opportunities Spring, Texas

Summary

I have worked in Labor and Delivery since 1984 as a staff nurse and as a charge nurse. I also worked as a house supervisor 12 years at one facility & 2 contracts at another facility. I also have experience as an occupational health nurse case manager. I hold RN licensure in Texas, California, Alaska, Washington, Oregon, Nevada, Alabama, Ohio, New Jersy, New York, and Massachusetts.

I am interested in a position in Case Management, House Supervisor, Labor & Delivery, or something new. I would like to work in north Houston, Spring, Cypress, & Conroe areas.

Experience

Axiom Medical Consulting LLC intake Nurse Case Manager November 2018 - March 2020 (1 year 5 months) The Woodlands, Texas, United States

occupational health Care Management

Kingwood Medical Center
Registered Nurse/Charge Nurse in Labor & Delivery
January 2017 - October 2018 (1 year 10 months)
Kingwood, TX

Labor and Delivery

Houston Northwest Medical Center Hospital RN/ Relief Charge Nurse in Labor & Delivery October 2015 - February 2017 (1 year 5 months) Houston, Texas

Peacehealth Ketchikan Medical Center House Supervisor May 2015 - October 2015 (6 months) Ketchikan, Alaska

KMC is a critical access hospital in the Alaskan rainforest. It is a 25-bed hospital on an island in Southeast Alaska. KMC is the only hospital for several hundred miles. Patients are evaluated in the ER and then dispositioned according to needs. They may be admitted or flown to Anchorage, Bellingham, or Seattle based on specialized care that is needed. I work nights as a house supervisor.

Hudson Staffing
Travel RN/Labor & Delivery Charge Nurse
January 2015 - April 2015 (4 months)
Laredo, Texas, United States

RN/CN in Labor and Delivery at Laredo Medical center, Laredo, Texas

Ketchikan Medical Center Hospital House Supervisor July 2014 - October 2014 (4 months) Ketchikan, Alaska

Travel assignment at a critical access facility.

Conroe Regional Medical Center Hospital House Supervisor/Labor & Delivery Charge Nurse May 1984 - June 2014 (30 years 2 months) Retired

Education

Grand Canyon University
BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2015 - 2016)

Houston Community College
ADN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1980 - 1984)